{
    "subject": "resource/Joaquin_Phoenix",
    "predicate": "property/relatives",
    "object": "resource/Rain_Phoenix",
    "human_readable": "Joaquin Phoenix's relative is Rain Phoenix.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9828877449035645,
            "question": "Is Rain Phoenix related to Joaquin Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9440036416053772,
            "question": "Who is Joaquin Phoenix's relative?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9111070036888123,
            "question": "Are Rain Phoenix and Joaquin Phoenix family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8970804214477539,
            "question": "Is there a familial link between Joaquin Phoenix and Rain Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8905693888664246,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Joaquin Phoenix and Rain Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8831627368927002,
            "question": "What is the name of Joaquin Phoenix's relative?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8553078770637512,
            "question": "What is the connection between Joaquin Phoenix and Rain Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8516781330108643,
            "question": "Do Joaquin Phoenix and Rain Phoenix share a common ancestor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7744424939155579,
            "question": "Can you name a famous relative of Joaquin Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7643797993659973,
            "question": "Who are some well-known individuals related to Joaquin Phoenix?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joaquin Phoenix's relative is Rain Phoenix.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5887_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous relative of Joaquin Phoenix?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5887_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do Joaquin Phoenix and Rain Phoenix share a common ancestor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5887_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the connection between Joaquin Phoenix and Rain Phoenix?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5887_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5887_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Joaquin Phoenix\u2019s relative is Rain Phoenix. Specifically, multiple files mention that Joaquin Phoenix has three sisters, including Rain Phoenix."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}